Everyone is suspect.
The Lodger is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by David Ondaatje.
Follows a seasoned detective on the trail of a ruthless killer intent on
slaughtering prostitutes along West Hollywood's Sunset Strip.
It appears that the murderer's grisly methods are identical to that of London's infamous 19th century
psychopath Jack the Ripper – a relentless serial killer who was never caught by police.
To make matters worse, the detective soon notices the parallels between the crimes committed by
the West Hollywood stalker and those of a serial murderer incarcerated years ago.
Could the wrong man be behind bars?
Chandler Manning, played by Alfred Molina.
Ellen Bunting, played by Hope Davis.
Street Wilkenson, played by Shane West.
Bunting, played by Donal Logue.
Captain Smith, played by Philip Baker Hall.
Amanda, played by Rachael Leigh Cook.
The Lodger is a 2009 mystery/thriller film directed by David Ondaatje
and starring Alfred Molina, Hope Davis and Simon Baker.
It is based on the 1913 novel The Lodger by Marie Belloc Lowndes, filmed previously by Alfred Hitchcock in 1927, by
Maurice Elvey in 1932, by John Brahm in 1944, and as Man in the Attic (1953) directed by Hugo Fregonese.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.